Christian Provido Front-end Web Developer Personal Info

Address

#16 San Marco St.Moonwalk Subd. Talon 5Las-Pinas City, Metro Manila, PH

Phone

+63 9163355644

E-mail

provido.calbert@gmail.com

WWW

battlecheeze.github.id

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/calbertprovide

Github

https://github.com/battlecheeze

Soft Skills

Communication

Advanced

Collaboration

Advanced

Hard skills

GIMP/Photoshop

Advanced

HTML/CSS

Advanced

JavaScript

Intermediate

Accomplished front-end and email developer motivated by challenging projects and fresh ideas. Extensive experience designing & building websites (using HTML5, CSS3 and various web scripting technologies) as well as responsive emails compatible in over 30+ email clients.

Experience

2019-05 -Present

ITMishelle

- Freelance Front End Developer support on contract basis
- Coordinating with Japanese clients and various small businesses to finalize designs and confirm requirements
- Creating custom mockups and developing intuitive UIs and Designing responsive webpages with accessibility standards in mind
- Testing frontend code in multiple browsers to ensure cross-browser compatibility

2018-01 -Present

The Defence Works

- Customise responsive cross-browser compatible landing pages using HTML(5), CSS(3), JS and jQuery
- Optimise & hand coded 90% of training emails and newsletters for custom events compatible in over 30+ email clients
- Test and troubleshoot HTML emails using Litmus.
- Worked as a Virtual Assistant and Lead Generation Specialist

2014-10 -

2017-09

• Data Researcher and Analyst For Mediamiser, Vuelio and AgilityPR Project

2008-07 -2012-08 SPi Global

Innodata

 Worked as Content Editor that handle responsibilities of on-time loading pages and contents of caselaw documents for LexisNexis Account

Education

2013-01 -

2013-02

Tekguru

• Training Comptia A+ Essentials 2009 Objectives with Practical Application

2002 -

AMA College of Las Pinas

2008

- Followed my passion developing websites and script pages
- Excelled in user experience and user interface work

Interest

Playing Boardgames, Mountain Biking, Studying and learning new web development technologies, Playing video games